turbotizer.com 2016-10-28

# Turbotizer – Revenue Share, Traffic Exchange 1:5 Ratio, Paid to Click, Advertising site.

**Warning** : Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /home/turbotizer/secure.docs/classes/class.db2.php:0) in **/home/turbotizer/public_html/globals.php** on line **229**

### Privacy Policy

This is the web site of Turbotizer.

We can be reached via Support form.

1.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?  
Turbotizer only contacts individuals who have registered at our website, or have purchased one of our products. Turbotizer collects personal identity information from our users during online registration and online purchasing. This information includes, name and email address to receive products and membership materials. All of this information is provided by the customer. 

2.

Contacting members via email:  
Under no circumstances do we ever ask for your password, account information or anything related to Turbotizer via e-mail. We do not send unauthorised emails to our members. 

3.

We use cookies:  
We use cookies to store some user data, under no circumstances is sensitive data (password, username, IP, etc.) stored in your cookies. We require cookies so that we can perform the following:  
• Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.  
• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.  
• Keep track of advertisements.  
• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.  

4.

If users disable cookies in their browser:  
If you disable cookies or turn off, some features will be disabled eg. Site Language, View Images Login Token, Validate Logins.   
It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.  
Your browser has to have cookies enabled for the website to function normally.

5.

How do we protect visitor information?  
Your information is stored on our secure server. Your information can only be accessed by the staff at Turbotizer. All passwords are encrypted, So even the staff at Turbotizer cannot see your password. Our site is secured using SSL Certificate to ensure no data is being hacked on registration. 

6.

Account security:  
We accumulate and store all user inputted information as well as your IP address browser information & date and time of the record conception upon registration. We store passwords in a one way encryption so it can't be reversed. User information such as your e-mail and Payment Gateway email/username will never be revealed. 

7.

Third Party Disclosure:  
For the privacy acts of Third party links to other sites which include banner, popup and text link adverts as well as general advertising links that may be displayed all throughout the Turbotizer website we do not take responsibility, you are viewing advertisements under your own will and risk.  
Your information is used for internal marketing purposes only. Turbotizer does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information (name, email, mailing address, etc.). Your information is not shared with any other third party or company outside of billing and shipping purposes. 

8.

Disclaimer:  
We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time, without notice. All members will be notified in the event of any Privacy Policy updates.
